I am from the insurance sector but we are in completely
opposite moves. First ICICI Pr
ICICI Pr is making day low at this time and
now ICICI Lombard is making
desi high in ICICI Pr First Life
Insurance and ICICI Lombard General
Insurance and see there are very different
textures, both the stocks will give good results
probably and Pro have already come in Pro, there was
talk of a block deal in Lombard for a long time, so because of that
it probably performed a little bit here,
but it is quite
interesting that at this time there is a move going on in it,
Prakash, please
tell me after looking at the chart of both the stocks, ICICI Pr and
ICICI Lombard, I will see you guys, if you
see, there
is actually a possibility of a reversal for the last 4 weeks,
when it crosses 520 then a reverse will be received, a
buy signal will be generated, so it
should not be done around 545, this much stretching shot is a bit
much, there may be more stress,
but 22 signal generator, it should be waited for above 520
That stretching here has been going on for about four to three weeks now. This is the
fourth after stretching. Here, I'm
trying to do a full back. There's
an aggressive wire here. Today's low is
around 1100. Super Stock. If it goes, it's
aggressive. It might reach
11:50 in the coming days. The
door opens for 1175.
[Music]
But I don't see much of a decline. We're
talking about it this morning. I think.